A Guide to the Miscellaneous political campaign material, 1956-1989
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Miscellaneous political campaign material,, 1956-1989
The Library of Virginia
27886
3.875 cu. ft. and 8 boxes
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Donor information unavailable.
Scope and Content
Miscellaneous political campaign material, 1956-1989, contains ads, brochures, campaign pins, correspondence, flyers, posters, sample ballots, and other material concerning elections for president; U.S. Senate and House of Representatives; Virginia State Senate and House of Delegates; Governor, Lieutenant Governor, and Attorney General; Richmond, Virginia, city council; and Commonwealth's Attorney. Contains sound recordings of campaign songs for Richard Nixon's 1972 presidential reelection and of campaign commercials for Gerald Baliles' 1985 governor's campaign. Collection also includes correspondence and mailings concerning the Republican, Democratic, American, and U.S. Labor Parties, as well as newsletters mailed to consituents by Senators and Congressmen. There is also a organizational chart for Virginia state government, materials on Republican state conventions, and other miscellaneous items.
Contents List
- Miscellaneous Political Campaign Materials,, 1956-1989. (Box 1-8)
  - Spiro Agnew--Vice President, 1972. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - George E. Allen--House of Delegates, 1959, 1973, 1975, 1977. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - J. Linday Almond/A. E. S. Stephens/Albertis Harrison--Governor/Lieutenant Governor/Attorney General, 1957. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - John M. Ambrose--Richmond City Council. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - John Anderson (Independent)--President, 1976. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Tom Anderson--Vice President, 1972. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Tom Anderson/Rufus Shackelford (American Party)--President/Vice President, 1976. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - T. Coleman Andrews--House of Delegates, 1959. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Rochelle A. Ascher/Anthony J. Van Zwaren/Robert A. Robinson (Labor Party)--Richmond City Council. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Bill Axselle--House of Delegates, 1973-1981, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bill Axselle, Bob Ball, Jim Jenkins, Fergie Reid--House of Delegates. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Margaret B. Baker--Henrico County Clerk of Circuit Court. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Tommy Baker--House of Delegates, 1989. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Dan Balfour--House of Delegates. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Gerald Baliles--House of Delegates, 1975[?]. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Gerald Baliles--Attorney General, 1981. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Gerald Baliles--Governor, 1985, folder 1 of 3. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Gerald Baliles--Governor, 1985, folder 2 of 3. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Gerald Baliles--Governor, 1985, folder 3 of 3. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Gerald Baliles/Doug Wilder/Mary Sue Terry--Governor/Lieutenant Governor/Attorney General, 1985. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Bob Ball--House of Delegates. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Herb Bateman--Lieutenant Governor, 1981. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Herb Bateman--Congress (non-election). (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Daniel Belanger--Richmond City Council. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Fitzgerald Bemiss--State Senate, 1959. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Peggy Bendrick--House of Delegates. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Joseph Benedetti--House of Delegates, 1982, 1983. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Joseph Benedetti--Attorney General, 1989. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Don Beyer--Lieutenant Governor, 1989. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Lloyd C. Bird--State Senate. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Tom Bliley--Congress, 1980. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Tom Bliley--Congress, 1982. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Tom Bliley--Congress, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Tom Bliley--Congress (non-election). (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Julian A. Bryant--House of Delegates. (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - George Bush--Vice President, 1984. (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Robert Y. Button--Attorney General, 1961, 1965. (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Earl Butz--Secretary of Agriculture, 1972. (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Harry F. Byrd, Jr.--U.S. Senate, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Harry F. Byrd, Jr.--U.S. Senate (non-election). (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Joe Canada--Lieutenant Governor, 1977. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Jimmy Carter--President, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Jimmy Carter/Walter Mondale--President/Vice President, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Jimmy Carter/Bud Zumwalt/David Satterfield--President/U.S. Senate/Congress, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Jimmy Carter/Walter Mondale--President/Vice President, 1980. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Howard H. Carwile--House of Delegates.. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - John Chichester--Lieutenant Governor, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Tom Coghill--House of Delegates.. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Thomas E. Coghill/Edwin H. Ragsdale/Julian A. Bryant--House of Delegates; Mills E. Godwin/John N. Dalton/Pat Echols--Governor/Lieutenant Governor/Attorney General, 1973. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Marshall Coleman--Attorney General, 1977. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Marshall Coleman--Governor, 1981, folder 1 of 2. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Marshall Coleman--Governor, 1981, folder 2 of 2. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Marshall Coleman/Nathan Miller/Wyatt Durrette--Governor/Lieutenant Governor/Attorney General, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Marshall Coleman--Governor, 1989. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Marshall Coleman/Eddy Dalton/Joseph Benedetti--Governor/Lieutenant Governor/Attorney General, 1989. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Jud Collier--Commonwealth's Attorney. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - E. Hatcher Crenshaw--Richmond City Council. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - E. Hatcher Crenshaw--House of Delegates. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - E. Hatcher Crenshaw/Chuck Walker--House of Delegates, 1979. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Eddy Dalton--Lieutenant Governor, 1989. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - John Dalton--Lieutenant Governor, 1973. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - John Dalton--Governor, 1977. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - John Dalton/Joe Canada/Marshall Coleman--Governor/Lieutenant Governor/Attorney General, 1977. (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Aubrey "Jerry" Davis--Commonwealth's Attorney. (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Dick Davis--Lieutenant Governor, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Dick Davis--U.S. Senate, 1982. (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Jim Davis--House of Delegates, 1977. (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Harold H. Dervishian--House of Delegates, 1959. (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Bob Dole--Vice President, 1976. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Sam Dudley--House of Delegates, 1977. (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Wyatt Durrette--Attorney General, 1977. (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Wyatt Durrette--Attorney General, 1981. (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Wyatt Durette--Governor, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Wyatt Durrette/John Chichester/William "Buster" O'Brien--Governor/Lieutenant Governor/Attorney General, 1985. (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - William M. Eagles--House of Delegates. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Coy Eaves--House of Delegates, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Pat Echols--Attorney General, 1973. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Walter Emroch--House of Delegates, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Guy Farley--Lieutenant Governor, 1981. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Geraldine Ferraro--Vice President, 1984. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Aubrey Fitzgerald--House of Delegates. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Nathan Forb--Richmond City Council, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Gerald Ford--President, 1976. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Gerald Ford/Bob Dole--President/Vice President, 1976. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Ray Garland--Congress, 1976[?]. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Ed Godsey--Richmond City Council. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Mills Godwin--Lieutenant Governor, 1961. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Mills Godwin/Fred G. Pollard/Robert Y. Button--Governor/Lieutenant Governor/Attorney General, 1965. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Mills Godwin--Governor, 1973. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Mills Godwin/John Dalton/Pat Echols--Governor/Lieutenant Governor/Attorney General, 1973. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Charles W. Gunn/Lacey E. Putney--House of Delegates. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Ed Haddock--State Senate, 1959. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Franklin P. Hall--House of Delegates, 1975, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Frank Hargrove--House of Delegates. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Albertis Harrison--Attorney General, 1957. (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Albertis Harrison/Mills E. Godwin/Robert Y. Button--Governor/Lieutenant Governor/Attorney General, 1961. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Edythe Harrison--U.S. Senate, 1984. (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Linwood Holton--U.S. Senate, 1978. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Henry Howell--Governor, 1973. (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Henry Howell--Governor, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Henry Howell/Chuck Robb/Ed Lane--Governor/Lieutenant Governor/Attorney General, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Rob James--House of Delegates. (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Rob James/Wayne O'Bryan--House of Delegates, 1981. (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Jim Jenkins--House of Delegates, 1973. (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Steve Kemp--Richmond City Council, 1978. (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Edward Kennedy--President, 1980. (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Karen Kincannon--House of Delegates, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Benjamin J. Lambert--House of Delegates. (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Ed Lane--House of Delegates, 1959, 1971, 1975. (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Ed Lane--Attorney General, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Lyndon LaRouche (Labor Party)--President, 1980. (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Ira M. Letchner--Lieutenant Governor, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Bill Leidinger--Richmond City Council. (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Theodore J. "Ted" Markow--House of Delegates, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Steve Martin--House of Delegates, 1989. (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - George McGovern--President, 1972. (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - George McGovern/Sargent Shriver--President/Vice President, 1972. (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Alex McMurtrie--House of Delegates, 1973. (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Harry Michael--Lieutenant Governor, 1973. (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Andy Miller--Attorney General, 1973. (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Andy Miller--Governor, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Nathan Miller--U.S. Senate, 1978. (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Nathan Miller--Lieutenant Governor, 1981. (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Walter Mondale--Vice President, 1976, 1980. (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Walter Mondale--President, 1984. (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Walter Mondale/Geraldine Ferraro--President/Vice President, 1984. (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Walter Mondale/Geraldine Ferraro/Edythe Harrison--President/Vice President/U.S. Senate, 1984. (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Michael Morchower--House of Delegates, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Phil Morris--State Senate.. (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Richard Nixon--President, 1972, folder 1 of 5. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Richard Nixon--President, 1972, folder 2 of 5. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Richard Nixon--President, 1972, folder 3 of 5. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Richard Nixon--President, 1972, folder 4 of 5. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Richard Nixon--President, 1972, folder 5 of 5. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Richard Nixon/Spiro Agnew--President/Vice President, 1972. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Richard Nixon/Spiro Agnew/William Scott--President/Vice President/U.S. Senate, 1972. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Richard Nixon/William Scott--President/U.S. Senate, 1972. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Dick Obenshain--U.S. Senate, 1978. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - William "Buster" O'Brien--Attorney General, 1985. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Wayne O'Bryan--House of Delegates, 1981, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Alan R. Ogden--Congress, 1978. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Thomas Nelson Parker--House of Delegates, 1959. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Fred G. Pollard--House of Delegates, 1959. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Fred G. Pollard--Lieutenant Governor, 1965. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Lacey E. Putney--House of Delegates,. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Edwin H. Ragsdale--House of Delegates, 1973. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Ronald Reagan--President, 1980. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Ronald Reagan--President, 1984. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Ronald Reagan/George Bush--President/Vice President, 1984. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Fergie Reid--House of Delegates,. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Jack Reid--House of Delegates. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Major Reynolds--House of Delegates. (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Major Reynolds--Lieutenant Governor, 1977. (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Chuck Robb--Lieutenant Governor, 1977. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Chuck Robb--Governor, 1981. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Chuck Robb/Dick Davis/Gerald Baliles--Governor/Lieutenant Governor/Attorney General, 1981. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - A. Willis Robertson--Congress. (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Robert A. Robinson--Richmond City Council. (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - George W. Rowe--Richmond City Council. (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - John G. Royster--House of Delegates. (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Rod Sager--Commonwealth's Attorney, 1977, 1981, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - David Satterfield--House of Delegates, 1959. (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - David Satterfield--Congress, 1976. (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - David Satterfield--Congress (non-election). (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - John G. Schmitz--President, 1972. (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - John G. Schmitz/Tom Anderson--President/Vice President, 1972. (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - William Scott--U.S. Senate, 1972. (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Rufus Shackelford--Vice President, 1976. (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Sargent Shriver--Vice President, 1972. (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - French Slaughter--Congress, 1984. (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Al Smith--House of Delegates, 1979. (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Muriel H. Smith--Richmond City Council. (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Shad Solomon--Lieutenant Governor, 1977. (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Dimitrios Soulis--Richmond City Council, 1978. (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - William Spong--U.S. Senate, 1972. (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - A. E. S. Stephens--Lieutenant Governor, 1957. (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Walter Stosch--House of Delegates, 1981. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - T. Dix Sutton--House of Delegates, 1973. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Eugene B. Sydnor--State Senate, 1959. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Mary Sue Terry--Attorney General, 1985. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Mary Sue Terry--Attorney General, 1989. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Aubrey H. Thompson--Richmond City Council, 1977. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Paul Trible--U.S. Senate, 1982. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Dorothy Ulrich Troubetzkoy--House of Delegates, 1973. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Henry L. Valentine--Richmond City Council, 1977. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Anthony J. Van Zwaren--Richmond City Council. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - John Waldrop--Congress, 1982. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Charles E. "Chuck" Walker--House of Delegates, 1979. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - James B. "Jim" Walthall--Richmond City Treasurer, 1977. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - John Warner--U.S. Senate, 1978. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - John Warner--U.S. Senate, 1984. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - John Warner--U.S. Senate (non-election). (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Ken Wells--Congress, 1972. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Doug Wilder--Lieutenant Governor, 1985. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Doug Wilder--Governor, 1989. (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Doug Wilder/Don Beyer/Mary Sue Terry--Governor/Lieutenant Governor/Attorney General, 1989. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Edward E. Willey--House of Delegates, 1959, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Frank Wolf--Congress (non-election). (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - James H. Young--Richmond City Treasurer, 1977. (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Elmo "Bud" Zumwalt--U.S. Senate, 1976. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Sample ballots, 1959-1989. (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - AARP voters' guide. (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Abuses of Power by the House Subcommittee on International Organizations. (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - ACA (Americans for Constitutional Action) Index, 1972. (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - AFL-CIO Committee on Political Education. (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - American Party, 1972, includes convention guide. (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Conservative Caucus. (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Crusade for Voters. (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Equal Rights Amendment. (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Guy Farley--National Republican Convention, 1980. (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Farm Prices and Food Prices, U.S. Department of Agriculture. (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - First Monday, November-December 1982. (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Labor for America Committee, 1972. (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Moral Majority. (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Principles and Pragmatism in American Foreign Policy," William P. Rogers, Secretary of State. (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - R.I.T.A. referendum (Richmond, Virginia). (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Republican Party fund raising, 1980-1982. (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Republican Party newsletters, 1977-1984. (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Republican State Conventions, 1977, 1978, 1980, 1981, 1982, 1984, 1985. (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Richard D. Obenshain Center. (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Skull and Bones, November 1977. (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Socialist Labor Party, 1972. (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Telephone bank. (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - U.S. Labor Party. (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Virginia State Government Organization chart, 1956. (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Virginia Taxpayers' Association. (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Virginia Republican Party miscellany. (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Virginia Democratic Party Miscellany. (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Miscellaneous items. (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Campaign buttons--George McGovern; George McGovern/Sargent Shriver; Richard Nixon; Richard Nixon/Spiro Agnew; John G. Schmitz; John G. Schmitz/Tom Anderson; John Anderson, 1972, 1980 (includes Richard Nixon pencil). (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Campaign buttons--William Scott; William Spong; Richard Obenshain, 1972, 1978. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Campaign buttons--Albertis Harrison/Mills Godwin/Robert Button; Mills Godwin/Fred Pollard/Robert Button; Henry Howell; Andy Miller, 1961, 1965, 1973, 1977. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Richard Nixon campaign record (President), 1972. (Box 6)
  - Gerald Baliles campaign commercials tape (Governor), 1985. (Box 6)
  - Bob Ball styrofoam football (House of Delegates). (Box 6)
  - Richard Nixon--President; Richard Nixon/Spiro Agnew--President/Vice President, 1972. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Richard Nixon--President, 1972. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Richard Nixon--President, 1972. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Jimmy Carter--President; Jimmy Carter/Walter Mondale--President/Vice President; Walter Mondale/Geraldine Ferraro--President/Vice President; Tom Anderson--Vice President, 1972-1984. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - William Scott--U.S. Senate, 1972. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - William Spong; Harry F. Byrd, Jr.; Bud Zumwalt; Dick Obenshain, John Warner--U.S. Senate, 1972-1978. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Mills Godwin--Governor, 1965. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Henry Howell--Governor, 1973, 1977. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - John Dalton--Governor, 1977. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Gerald Baliles/Doug Wilder/Mary Sue Terry--Governor/Lieutenant Governor/Attorney General, 1985. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Doug Wilder/Don Beyer/Mary Sue Terry--Governor/Lieutenant Governor/Attorney General, 1989. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Marshall Coleman/Eddy Dalton/Joseph Benedetti--Governor/Lieutenant Governor/Attorney General, 1989. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Andy Miller--Attorney General. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - T. Dix Sutton; Gerald Baliles; Bill Axselle/Bob Ball/Jim Jenkins/Fergie Reid; Bill Axselle/Bob Ball/Rob James/Wayne O'Bryan--House of Delegates, 1973, 1975, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Nathan Forb and George W. Rowe--Richmond City Council. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Newsletters of Congressmen Tom Bliley and Frank Wolf, 1982, 1984. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous materials. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - George McGovern--President; Richard Nixon--President; John G. Schmitz--President; Tom Anderson--Vice President; William Scott--U.S. Senate, 1972. (Cabinet 10, Drawer 3)